{
    "subject": "resource/Percy_the_Small_Engine",
    "predicate": "ontology/voice",
    "object": "resource/Keith_Wickham",
    "human_readable": "Percy the Small Engine is voiced by Keith Wickham.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9342396855354309,
            "question": "Who voices Percy the Small Engine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8377852439880371,
            "question": "Which character is voiced by Keith Wickham?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6926876306533813,
            "question": "What is the name of the show featuring Percy the Small Engine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6775544881820679,
            "question": "What makes Keith Wickham's portrayal of Percy distinctive?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5786520838737488,
            "question": "What is the genre of the show featuring Percy the Small Engine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5225680470466614,
            "question": "In what type of media does Percy the Small Engine appear?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4064193665981293,
            "question": "Is Keith Wickham known for voicing any other characters?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40587908029556274,
            "question": "Who are some other voice actors in the show with Percy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36725232005119324,
            "question": "What is the name of the actor who provides the voice for Percy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3057023584842682,
            "question": "Does Keith Wickham have any other notable roles?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Percy the Small Engine is voiced by Keith Wickham.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4408_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the actor who provides the voice for Percy?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4408_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are some other voice actors in the show with Percy?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4408_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Keith Wickham known for voicing any other characters?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4408_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4408_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4408_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4408_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4408_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4408_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4408_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4408_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4408_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4408_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4408_81.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. According to file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_4408/re-ranker-msmarco/75.txt, Keith Wickham is a British voice actor known for providing the voices of various characters in the children's television series Thomas & Friends, and one of those characters is Percy."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that states \"Percy the Small Engine Gender: Male Number: NWR 6 Basis: Avonside 0-4-0ST Railway: North Western Railway UK Voice Actor: Keith Wickham (2009-2015), Nigel Pilkington (2015-2021), Christopher Ragland (2016; singing voice) US Voice Actor: Martin Sherman (2009-2015), Christopher Ragland (2014-2021)\". This confirms that Keith Wickham has indeed voiced Percy the Small Engine during a specific period."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}